http://www.accpe.com/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting ACCPE. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected here at ACCPE.com. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for ACCPE only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, and billing information when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your order request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific purchase request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
We may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. In plain English, we use this information to improve your overall experience and to know what works best.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. It is for your protection only.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. Rest assured, your information is safe with ACCPE.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: info@accpe.com
By Phone: 800-394-6275
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted with the last updated date clearly posted at the top of this page.
Continue
About us
The American Center for Continuing Professional Education offers affordable self-study CPE for CPAs, enrolled agents, tax preparers and students interested in furthering their education.
Our courses are available in the following formats: Textbook, PDF, and Exam Only. We also offer some On-Demand and Webinar courses.
Find more information on our CPA Education blog.
Connect with us on social media for information on CPE requirements, CPA news and special offers.
